blueshirtsunited.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy - The Madison Square Garden Company

The MSG Family is committed to safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy ("Policy") is to ensure that you understand the measures the MSG Family takes in order to protect your information and to provide transparency regarding what information it collects, how we use it, and when and with whom we may share it. The Policy applies to any and all websites, applications (including but not limited to mobile applications), software and any other electronic and/or digital products and/or services (and any and all content, features, applications or functions offered or made available on or through any such website, application, software or other electronic and/or digital product or service) that are made available by the MSG Family (including, without limitation, e-mail notifications and social networking features (collectively, the "Services"). This Policy applies regardless of the device used to access the Services (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future). All Services that are governed by this Policy will include a link to, and/or copy of this Policy on the home page of the applicable website or similar location (e.g, a settings page) for any applicable mobile applications.

This Policy applies only to information collected on or through the Services as defined above. It does not apply to information collected or obtained by or through any other means (including, without limitation, information collected offline, in-person, over the telephone or by mail, e.g., from a telephonic survey, mail-in sweepstakes entry form and/or in-person at an event.

For purposes of this Policy, the terms "MSG Family," “MSG,” “we,” and “our” include, without limitation, The Madison Square Garden Company, MSG Holdings, L.P. and each of their respective parent companies, subsidiaries, divisions, affiliated entities and business units as may change from time to time (including, without limitation, MSG Sports, New York Knicks, New York Rangers, New York Liberty, MSG Entertainment, the Arena and Theater at Madison Square Garden, Radio City Music Hall, The Beacon Theatre, The Chicago Theatre, The Forum, MSG Media, MSG Networks, Fuse Networks and MSG Interactive).

Before you submit any information on or through the Services, please carefully review this Policy. By using any part of the Services, you consent to the collection, use, disclosure and sharing of your information as further outlined below in this Policy. We will continue to evaluate this Policy as we update and expand the Services and our offerings, and we may make changes to the Policy accordingly. Any changes will be posted here and you should check this page periodically for updates. Your continued use of the Services will signify acceptance of the terms of the updated Policy.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
When you register for an account, use the Services, participate in a contest, or make a purchase, you may be prompted to provide, on a voluntary basis, certain personally identifiable information about yourself, including, but not limited to, your: (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) age; (iv) mailing address; (v) hobbies; (vi) sports and entertainment interests; (vii) telephone number; (viii) fax number; (ix) viewpoints on certain events; and/or (x) in certain circumstances, payment and identity verification information, such as (1) credit card number, (2) social security number (or comparable national identifier) and/or (3) driver’s license number, when needed for payment in connection with a purchase. While you are not required to provide any such personally identifiable information, certain Services may not be accessible or available, absent account registration and/or your provision of the requested information.

We may collect location information, including general information (e.g., IP address, zip code) and more specific information (e.g., GPS-based location information) from your computer and/or mobile device and use that information to deliver content and advertising, based on your current location. If you access the Services from a mobile device and you do not want to provide us with GPS-based location information, you can disable the GPS or other location-tracking functions on your device or the location-based features of the mobile application (if applicable) using the following instructions which may be amended from time to time by the applicable providers:

•    If you are using an Apple device, click on “General,” then “Reset,” then “Reset Location and Privacy.” This will turn off location functionality for all of your applications so that the next time you download or use an application, you will be asked again to provide your consent for us and others to access your location information.

•    If you are using an Android device, visit device settings, click “Location,” and then click the boxes for the particular applications for which you would like to disable location services.

•    If your device changes the above-methods of disabling the collection of mobile device location, please contact your device manufacturer or platform provider to determine how to disable the collection of this location information.

If you access the Services through a third-party connection or log-in (e.g., through a social network), we may also collect your public user ID associated with that third-party service and any information you have made public in connection with the third-party service.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. If you choose to post User Content (as described in our [Terms of Service](http://www.thegarden.com/global/terms-of-service.html)) through the Services, such as via social networking services, on message boards, chat areas, comments and/or other postings, that information; (i) is publicly available; (ii) may be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge; and (iii) may result in your receipt of unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.

**COOKIES AND OTHER ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGIES**  
We may also collect data about your use of the Services through the use of Internet server logs, cookies and/or tracking pixels. A web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you visit a website, that enables us to recognize your computer, store your preferences and settings, enhance your user experience by delivering content specific to your interests, perform searches and analytics and assist with security administrative functions. Some cookies are placed in your browser cache while those associated with Flash technologies are stored with your Adobe Flash Player files. Tracking pixels (sometimes referred to as web beacons or clear GIFs) are tiny electronic tags with a unique identifier embedded in websites, online ads and/or email, and that are designed to provide usage information like ad impressions or clicks, measure popularity of the Services and associated advertising, and to access user cookies. We may also use these automated technologies to collect and analyze other non-personal information related to the devices you use to access the Services, such as IP addresses, browser types, browser language, and unique device identifiers and other information about your computer(s) and/or mobile device(s).

Please note that you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., [Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies); [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en); [Mozilla Firefox](http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox); or [Apple Safari](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042)). You can also manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at [Adobe's website](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html). Please note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features or offerings of the Services.

We use third parties to assist us in serving advertisements, tracking aggregated and/or anonymized site usage statistics, and providing content-sharing services to support the Services. These third parties may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect similar non-personal information about your use of the Services. We do not control these third-party technologies, and their use is governed by those parties' privacy policies.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**  
MSG may use your information for the following purposes:

•    For the purposes for which you provided it;"  
•    To send you information about your relationship or transactions with us;  
•    To send you alerts or other communications via SMS messages or other media or networks;  
•    To notify you about new features and offerings of the Services, including, but not limited to, discounts, events, shows news about our Services, products, other services, and/or special offers;  
•    To administer sweepstakes and contests;  
•    To process and respond to your inquiries;  
•    To contact you with information that we believe may be of interest to you;  
•    To attribute content that you make available through the Services;  
•    For internal research and reporting;  
•    To improve the content and features of the Services or develop new Services;  
•    To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you see on the Services (see Personalized Content and Advertising section below);  
•    To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Services;  
•    To administer and troubleshoot the Services; and  
•    To share your information with reputable third parties who may provide you with information about their products and/or services that may be of interest to you.

We may also combine information that we collect from you with information we obtain about you from other members of the MSG Family and/or non-affiliated third parties.

We may aggregate and/or anonymize information collected through the Services. We may use anonymous or aggregated data for any purpose, including for research and marketing purposes, and may also share such data with any third parties, including without limitation, advertisers, promotional partners, sponsors, event promoters, and/or others.

**WHEN WE DISCLOSE USER INFORMATION**  
The MSG Family of companies may disclose and/or share your information to or with any non-affiliated third parties under the following circumstances.

**Consent** : If you consent to the disclosure, we may do so.

**Service Providers**. We may provide access to your information to select third parties who perform services on our behalf and for any other legitimate business purposes. These third parties provide a variety of services to us, including without limitation, ticket processing, billing, sales, marketing, advertising, market research, fulfillment, data storage, analysis and processing, and legal services. MSG generally seeks contractual assurances from these service providers that they will not use your information in any manner other than to help us provide you with the services and products available from MSG.

**Other Third Parties**. Unless you direct us not to, we may share your information with reputable third parties so that they may contact you to offer products, services and promotions, such as sweepstakes and contests, that you may find valuable. You can instruct us not to provide your personal information to these third parties by sending an email to [privacychoices@msg.com](mailto:privacychoices@msg.com) with “REMOVE THIRD PARTIES” in the subject line. If you receive a communication from a third party and you do not wish to receive future communications from that party, you should also tell them to remove you from their marketing list.

**Protection of MSG and Others**. By using the Services, you acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve and disclose your information, including, but not limited to, any user content, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce our [Terms of Service](http://www.thegarden.com/global/terms-of-service.html), this Policy, or other contracts with you; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; and/or (e) protect the rights, property or personal safety of MSG, its agents and affiliates, its users and/or the public. We may also disclose information to law enforcement agencies in emergency circumstances, where the disclosure of such information is consistent with the types of emergency disclosures permitted or required by law.

**Business Transfers**. We reserve the right to disclose and transfer all of your information, including your personal information, to a successor company in connection with a merger, acquisition or sale of all, or components, of our business.

**CONSENT TO TRANSFER**  
The Services are operated in the United States. If you are a resident of the European Union or other location outside the United States, please be advised that any information you provide through the Services will be transferred to the United States or other designated locations outside of the United States for certain processing/hosting operations. We have taken commercially reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is appropriately protected and is processed only in accordance with this Policy. By using the Services, you consent to this transfer and to the use of the personal information as described herein.

**OPTING OUT OF USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR MARKETING PURPOSES BY MSG FAMILY**  
If you have provided personal information while using the Services and later decide that you would rather not have the MSG Family use personally identifiable information for marketing purposes in accordance with this Policy, you can opt-out of future use at any time by: (i) going to the link provided at the bottom of any email you receive from a MSG Family member and opting out of receiving information from that MSG Family member; (ii) by sending us an email at [privacychoices@msg.com](mailto:privacychoices@msg.com); or (iii) writing us at MSG Holdings, L.P., 2 Penn Plaza, 16th Floor, New York, New York, 10012, Attn: Vice President, Engagement Marketing and with a copy to Vice President, Legal and Business Affairs, Entertainment at the same address.

**PERSONALIZED CONTENT AND ADVERTISING AND YOUR CHOICES**  
We may personalize the content and advertising that you see when using the Services through the use of third-party advertising technologies that allow for the delivery of relevant content and advertising on MSG websites or applications. You can learn more about personalized advertising through consumer education materials provided by the Digital Advertising Alliance [here](http://www.aboutads.info/).

If you do not wish to receive personalized advertising when using a MSG website, third parties who deliver those advertisements allow you to opt-out [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). MSG does not control this third-party provided opt-out process. If you do not wish to receive personalized advertising when using a MSG mobile application, you have the following options: If you are using an iOS (Apple) device to access the Services you may opt-out by accessing the following link on your mobile device: http://oo.apple.com. If you are using an iOS6 device, you also may limit the delivery of personalized advertisement by: Open Settings and tap “General” then tap “About”; Scroll to the bottom of About and tap “Advertising”; Flip “Limit Ad Tracking” to ON. If you are using an Android device and you do not wish to receive personalized in-application advertisements, you can visit Google’s Ads Preferences page from a browser on your device and make your choices there. We do not control how the applicable platform operator allows you to control receiving personalized in-application advertisements; thus, you should contact the platform provider if any of the above-options are no longer available.

Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive advertisements even if you opt-out. In that case, the advertising will not be tailored to your interests.

**UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION**  
To keep your information accurate, current and complete, visit your account page(s) or email [privacychoices@msg.com](mailto:privacychoices@msg.com) to update and/or correct any information previously provided. If a member name and password are required to access the feature, you will need to provide such information to update your registration information. If you have forgotten your password, you may obtain it by visiting the registration area and requesting that a hint be sent to you at the email address you originally provided during registration.

**LINKS**  
Links to third-party websites, applications and other services may be made available through the Services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party services. Any information you provide via those services is subject to the applicable privacy policies and is not covered by this Policy.

**SECURITY**  
We have implemented commercially reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and/or alteration of your information. However, we cannot and do not guarantee that these measures will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use, or disclose your information since despite our efforts, no Internet and/or other electronic transmissions can be completely secure.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**  
California Law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacychoices@msg.com](mailto:privacychoices@msg.com) or write to us at MSG Holdings, L.P., 2 Pennsylvania Plaza, 16th Floor, New York, New York 10012, Attn: Vice President, Engagement Marketing and with a copy to Vice President, Legal and Business Affairs, Entertainment and the same address.

**INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN**  
MSG does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information directly from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to MSG. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe MSG has any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**CONTACTING US ABOUT THIS POLICY**  
Please do not hesitate to contact us with any questions, concerns, requests or comments by email at [msgfeedback@msg.com](mailto:msgfeedback@msg.com) or write to us at MSG Holdings, L.P., 2 Pennsylvania Plaza, 16th Floor, New York, New York 10012, Attn: Vice President, Engagement Marketing and with a copy to Vice President, Legal and Business Affairs, Entertainment at the same address.

Effective Date: October 1, 2013

© Copyright 1999-2013 MSG Holdings, L.P. 2 Pennsylvania Plaza, New York, NY 10121-0091. All rights reserved. Use of the Service which include a link to this Policy signifies your acceptance of this Policy.

Thank you for visiting!
